<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>top on NewsStreet | News portal</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/top/</link>
    <description>Recent content in top on NewsStreet | News portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:29:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak, wife Akshata Murthy&#39;s combined fortune is double of UK&#39;s King Charles</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-wife-akshata-murthys-combined-fortune-is-double-of-uks-king-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-wife-akshata-murthys-combined-fortune-is-double-of-uks-king-/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak, wife Akshata Murthy&amp;rsquo;s combined fortune is double of UK&amp;rsquo;s King Charles Rishi Sunak, who has become the UK&#39;s first ever Hindu Prime Minister, and wife Akshata Murthy, daughter of Indian billionaire NR Narayana Murthy, have a combined fortune of 730 million pounds, media reports claimed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chhat Puja 2022: Important dates from Arghya to Kharna</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/chhat-puja-2022-important-dates-from-arghya-to-kharna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/chhat-puja-2022-important-dates-from-arghya-to-kharna/</guid>
      <description>Chhat Puja 2022: Important dates from Arghya to Kharna During Chhat puja the Sun God and Chhati Mata are worshipped, and both men and women fast for 36 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAG set to conduct comprehensive audit of country&#39;s health sector</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cag-set-to-conduct-comprehensive-audit-of-countrys-health-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cag-set-to-conduct-comprehensive-audit-of-countrys-health-sector/</guid>
      <description>CAG set to conduct comprehensive audit of country&amp;rsquo;s health sector Current approach to be based in common parameters, goals and analysis, as opposed to earlier exercises done on the basis of some research or state-specific issues</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laurus Labs hits 4-month low; stock slips 14% in 3 days post mixed Q2FY23</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/laurus-labs-hits-4-month-low-stock-slips-14-in-3-days-post-mixed-q2fy23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/laurus-labs-hits-4-month-low-stock-slips-14-in-3-days-post-mixed-q2fy23/</guid>
      <description>Laurus Labs hits 4-month low; stock slips 14% in 3 days post mixed Q2FY23 Despite mixed Q2FY23 performance, brokerages retain their &#39;buy&#39; rating on Laurus Labs with a target price in the range of Rs 610 and Rs 630 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgian tennis player Maryna Zanevska captures WTA 125 Rouen championship</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/belgian-tennis-player-maryna-zanevska-captures-wta-125-rouen-championship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/belgian-tennis-player-maryna-zanevska-captures-wta-125-rouen-championship/</guid>
      <description>Belgian tennis player Maryna Zanevska captures WTA 125 Rouen championship Zanevska defeated No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhang Zhizhen becomes first-ever Chinese man to enter ATP top 100</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/zhang-zhizhen-becomes-first-ever-chinese-man-to-enter-atp-top-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/zhang-zhizhen-becomes-first-ever-chinese-man-to-enter-atp-top-100/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Zhizhen becomes first-ever Chinese man to enter ATP top 100 Zhang Zhizhen became the first ever Chinese man to break into the ATP top 100 next week despite losing his Naples quarterfinal with Mackenzie McDonald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Wang, Sun crowned at World Table Tennis Champions Macao 2022</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/chinas-wang-sun-crowned-at-world-table-tennis-champions-macao-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/chinas-wang-sun-crowned-at-world-table-tennis-champions-macao-2022/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Wang, Sun crowned at World Table Tennis Champions Macao 2022 Chinese paddlers Wang Chuqin, and Sun Yingsha were crowned champions in the men’s and women’s singles finals at the World Table Tennis (WTT) Champions Macao 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepavali: Chennai police book 354 cases for violation of firecracker norms</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/deepavali-chennai-police-book-354-cases-for-violation-of-firecracker-norms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/deepavali-chennai-police-book-354-cases-for-violation-of-firecracker-norms/</guid>
      <description>Deepavali: Chennai police book 354 cases for violation of firecracker norms Most of the cases were booked for violations in the time stipulations given for bursting of firecrackers; a majority of the cases were in Mylapore, Washermenpet and Pulianthope, police said</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak to become Britain’s third PM of the year at meeting with King Charles III</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-to-become-britains-third-pm-of-the-year-at-meeting-with-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-to-become-britains-third-pm-of-the-year-at-meeting-with-king/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak to become Britain’s third PM of the year at meeting with King Charles III Liz Truss will depart after making a brief public statement, seven weeks to the day after she was appointed Prime Minister</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karnataka: Staff from government-aided schools, colleges demand pension. Threaten to go on hunger strike</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karnataka-staff-from-government-aided-schools-colleges-demand-pension-th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karnataka-staff-from-government-aided-schools-colleges-demand-pension-th/</guid>
      <description>Karnataka: Staff from government-aided schools, colleges demand pension. Threaten to go on hunger strike The President of the Pensionless Employees Association said that employees appointed after 2006 are getting pensions under either the Open or New Pension Schemes Members of the Pensionless Employees Association, who are in schools and colleges that are aided by the state government of Karnataka, have threatened to launch an indefinite hunger strike along with their family members at Freedom Park in Bengaluru if the Karnataka government does not announce pensions before December 19, stated a report by The New Indian Express.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UGC frames new guidelines on safety of women in educational institutions</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ugc-frames-new-guidelines-on-safety-of-women-in-educational-institutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ugc-frames-new-guidelines-on-safety-of-women-in-educational-institutions/</guid>
      <description>UGC frames new guidelines on safety of women in educational institutions Suggestions and comments are invited by the commission till November 14; a committee set up by UGC to review and update safety guidelines</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#WhatTheFAQ: Rishi Sunak is UK&#39;s new PM. Here&#39;s a look at the first Indian-origin PM&#39;s journey</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/whatthefaq-rishi-sunak-is-uks-new-pm-heres-a-look-at-the-first-indian-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/whatthefaq-rishi-sunak-is-uks-new-pm-heres-a-look-at-the-first-indian-/</guid>
      <description>#WhatTheFAQ: Rishi Sunak is UK&amp;rsquo;s new PM. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the first Indian-origin PM&amp;rsquo;s journey The 42-year-old has his roots in India and is the husband of Akshata Murty, daughter of Infosys Founder NR Narayan Murty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP govt. makes changes to Jagananna Gorumudda regarding distribution of eggs</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ap-govt-makes-changes-to-jagananna-gorumudda-regarding-distribution-of-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ap-govt-makes-changes-to-jagananna-gorumudda-regarding-distribution-of-egg/</guid>
      <description>AP govt. makes changes to Jagananna Gorumudda regarding distribution of eggs It is known that the government of Andhra Pradesh is giving importance to the quality of nutritious food provided to students studying in schools andonitoring the scheme from time to time and making necessary changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man turns his right eye socket into a flashlight after losing eyeball to cancer</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/man-turns-his-right-eye-socket-into-a-flashlight-after-losing-eyeball-to-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/man-turns-his-right-eye-socket-into-a-flashlight-after-losing-eyeball-to-ca/</guid>
      <description>Man turns his right eye socket into a flashlight after losing eyeball to cancer The future of body modding is here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kantara makers face allegations of plagiarism, Kerala band Thaikkudam Bridge to sue for copyright infringement</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/kantara-makers-face-allegations-of-plagiarism-kerala-band-thaikkudam-bridg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/kantara-makers-face-allegations-of-plagiarism-kerala-band-thaikkudam-bridg/</guid>
      <description>Kantara makers face allegations of plagiarism, Kerala band Thaikkudam Bridge to sue for copyright infringement The Kerala-based band has alleged similarities between Kantara’s ‘Varaha Roopam’ and its 2017 song ‘Navarasam’</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 dead, 39 persons hospitalised following diarrhoea and vomiting in Karnataka</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/3-dead-39-persons-hospitalised-following-diarrhoea-and-vomiting-in-karnata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/3-dead-39-persons-hospitalised-following-diarrhoea-and-vomiting-in-karnata/</guid>
      <description>3 dead, 39 persons hospitalised following diarrhoea and vomiting in Karnataka Villagers suspect that the deceased, and those admitted to hospital, had been consuming contaminated water, which is being supplied to each house through individual taps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin (BTC) Outclasses Major Fiat Currencies And Equities In Q3</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bitcoin-btc-outclasses-major-fiat-currencies-and-equities-in-q3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bitcoin-btc-outclasses-major-fiat-currencies-and-equities-in-q3/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin (BTC) Outclasses Major Fiat Currencies And Equities In Q3 Bitcoin, the de facto leader of all cryptocurrencies, will be entering the month of November this 2022 with trading price that is severely subpar with what it had the same month last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German President Frank-Walter Steinmeier makes surprise visit to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/german-president-frank-walter-steinmeier-makes-surprise-visit-to-ukraine-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/german-president-frank-walter-steinmeier-makes-surprise-visit-to-ukraine-am/</guid>
      <description>German President Frank-Walter Steinmeier makes surprise visit to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia German President Frank-Walter Steinmeier said after arriving in Kyiv that it was important to me in this phase of air attacks with drones, cruise missiles and rockets by Russia to send a signal of solidarity to Ukrainians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dove, other Unilever aerosol dry shampoos recalled over cancer risk</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dove-other-unilever-aerosol-dry-shampoos-recalled-over-cancer-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dove-other-unilever-aerosol-dry-shampoos-recalled-over-cancer-risk/</guid>
      <description>Dove, other Unilever aerosol dry shampoos recalled over cancer risk Unilever Plc recalled popular brands of aerosol dry shampoo, including Dove, after discovering they were contaminated with a chemical called benzene that can cause cancer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TS EAMCET 2022: Final phase seat allotment to be released on October 26. Here is how you can check</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ts-eamcet-2022-final-phase-seat-allotment-to-be-released-on-october-26-he/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ts-eamcet-2022-final-phase-seat-allotment-to-be-released-on-october-26-he/</guid>
      <description>TS EAMCET 2022: Final phase seat allotment to be released on October 26.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T20 World Cup 2022: Hardik Pandya make HUGE statement on &#39;Mankading&#39;, says &#39;to hell with Spirit of game&#39;</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/t20-world-cup-2022-hardik-pandya-make-huge-statement-on-mankading-says-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/t20-world-cup-2022-hardik-pandya-make-huge-statement-on-mankading-says-/</guid>
      <description>T20 World Cup 2022: Hardik Pandya make HUGE statement on &amp;lsquo;Mankading&amp;rsquo;, says &amp;lsquo;to hell with Spirit of game&amp;rsquo; The issue became a hot topic of discussion when Deepti Sharma ran out Charlie Dean at the non-striker&#39;s end for leaving her crease too early and handed India a historic 3-0 clean sweep in women&#39;s ODI series in England, last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</guid>
      <description>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam A total of nine candidates in the Sonitpur district have brought laurels to the district by achieving different ranks in the recently declared results of the APSC CCE 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The last of Corbusier’s gifts to India</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/the-last-of-corbusiers-gifts-to-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/the-last-of-corbusiers-gifts-to-india/</guid>
      <description>The last of Corbusier’s gifts to India On Corbusier’s 135th birth anniversary this month, a 1960-dated console desk in teak wood, designed by him and BV Doshi, went under the hammer for roughly ₹1 crore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jabalpur News: ‘होश तो आता है, लेकिन हादसे की याद उसे बेहोश कर देती है..’, पिंटू की दर्दनाक दास्तान</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jabalpur-news-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jabalpur-news-/</guid>
      <description>Jabalpur News: ‘होश तो आता है, लेकिन हादसे की याद उसे बेहोश कर देती है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian PM Giorgia Meloni thanks Tibetan spiritual leader Dalai Lama</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/italian-pm-giorgia-meloni-thanks-tibetan-spiritual-leader-dalai-lama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 06:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/italian-pm-giorgia-meloni-thanks-tibetan-spiritual-leader-dalai-lama/</guid>
      <description>Italian PM Giorgia Meloni thanks Tibetan spiritual leader Dalai Lama Italian PM Giorgia Meloni thanked Tibetan spiritual leader the Dalai Lama for the message of affection by him on her appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Biden Hosts Biggest-Ever Diwali Celebration in the White House</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/joe-biden-hosts-biggest-ever-diwali-celebration-in-the-white-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 06:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/joe-biden-hosts-biggest-ever-diwali-celebration-in-the-white-house/</guid>
      <description>Joe Biden Hosts Biggest-Ever Diwali Celebration in the White House Many Hindus, Jains, Sikhs, and Buddhists live in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India will always stand with the Global South, says External Affairs Minister S Jaishankar</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/india-will-always-stand-with-the-global-south-says-external-affairs-minist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/india-will-always-stand-with-the-global-south-says-external-affairs-minist/</guid>
      <description>India will always stand with the Global South, says External Affairs Minister S Jaishankar S Jaishankar articulated both infringements of India’s core interests as well as issues of pressing global concern including the long impending UN reforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘The Last of Us Part 1’ review: A masterpiece made even better</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/the-last-of-us-part-1-review-a-masterpiece-made-even-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/the-last-of-us-part-1-review-a-masterpiece-made-even-better/</guid>
      <description>‘The Last of Us Part 1’ review: A masterpiece made even better For a remake of a game that came out in 2013, it is still better than many of the present-day ones</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI hits record high on hopes of strong Q2 earnings; stock up 11% in 8 days</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/sbi-hits-record-high-on-hopes-of-strong-q2-earnings-stock-up-11-in-8-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/sbi-hits-record-high-on-hopes-of-strong-q2-earnings-stock-up-11-in-8-days/</guid>
      <description>SBI hits record high on hopes of strong Q2 earnings; stock up 11% in 8 days SBI&#39;s core fundamentals continue to be on a strong footing and improvement in systemic growth should drive incremental re-rating for the stock, according to analysts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan convinces Saudi Arabia to set up $12 bn refinery, petrochemical complex</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pakistan-convinces-saudi-arabia-to-set-up-12-bn-refinery-petrochemical-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pakistan-convinces-saudi-arabia-to-set-up-12-bn-refinery-petrochemical-co/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan convinces Saudi Arabia to set up $12 bn refinery, petrochemical complex The Pakistani side, according to the report, made huge efforts to persuade the kingdom to honour the MoUs and invest in the South Asian nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delhi University admissions: CSAS Round II begins today, October 25. Important details here</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/delhi-university-admissions-csas-round-ii-begins-today-october-25-import/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/delhi-university-admissions-csas-round-ii-begins-today-october-25-import/</guid>
      <description>Delhi University admissions: CSAS Round II begins today, October 25. Important details here Over 72,800 candidates out of 80,164 have accepted the college and course allotted to them in Delhi University&#39;s first round of seat allocations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top news developments in Karnataka on October 25, 2022</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/top-news-developments-in-karnataka-on-october-25-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/top-news-developments-in-karnataka-on-october-25-2022/</guid>
      <description>Top news developments in Karnataka on October 25, 2022 Here are the key news developments to watch out for from Karnataka today</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punjab government to sensitise people on gender-based violence on October 27</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/punjab-government-to-sensitise-people-on-gender-based-violence-on-october-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 05:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/punjab-government-to-sensitise-people-on-gender-based-violence-on-october-2/</guid>
      <description>Punjab government to sensitise people on gender-based violence on October 27 The Punjab government would organise a state-level awareness function in Jalandhar on October 27 to further sensitise people on gender-based violence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin Prime Minister of UK</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-prime-minister-of-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-prime-minister-of-uk/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin Prime Minister of UK Britain&#39;s Conservative Party leader Rishi Sunak becomes the first Indian-origin and Hindu Prime Minister of the United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court sets aside high court order granting bail to accused arrested with morphine</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/supreme-court-sets-aside-high-court-order-granting-bail-to-accused-arrested/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/supreme-court-sets-aside-high-court-order-granting-bail-to-accused-arrested/</guid>
      <description>Supreme Court sets aside high court order granting bail to accused arrested with morphine The Supreme Court has set aside a Gauhati High Court order which granted bail to two men, accused of possessing about 13 kg of morphine in a motor vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;It has power to bring light to world&#39;: Joe Biden lights a diya, hosts largest-ever Diwali reception at White House</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/it-has-power-to-bring-light-to-world-joe-biden-lights-a-diya-hosts-larg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/it-has-power-to-bring-light-to-world-joe-biden-lights-a-diya-hosts-larg/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;It has power to bring light to world&amp;rsquo;: Joe Biden lights a diya, hosts largest-ever Diwali reception at White House US President Joe Biden hosted a Diwali reception at the White House which was attended by more than 200 eminent Indian Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bidens host largest ever Deepavali reception at White House</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bidens-host-largest-ever-deepavali-reception-at-white-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bidens-host-largest-ever-deepavali-reception-at-white-house/</guid>
      <description>Bidens host largest ever Deepavali reception at White House More than 200 eminent Indian Americans attended the reception at the East Room of the White House, which saw cultural events including performances by sitarist Rishab Sharma and dance troupe The Sa Dance Company</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak&#39;s prize for predicting Truss chaos: He gets to clean up the mess</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/sunaks-prize-for-predicting-truss-chaos-he-gets-to-clean-up-the-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/sunaks-prize-for-predicting-truss-chaos-he-gets-to-clean-up-the-mess/</guid>
      <description>Sunak&amp;rsquo;s prize for predicting Truss chaos: He gets to clean up the mess Just seven weeks after Truss traveled to meet Queen Elizabeth II to become premier, Sunak will meet King Charles III on Tuesday to formally replace her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning Digest | Look forward to working together on global issues, says PM Modi on Sunak’s elevation; V-Cs can continue till Governor takes decision on show cause notice, says Kerala HC, and more</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/morning-digest-look-forward-to-working-together-on-global-issues-says-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/morning-digest-look-forward-to-working-together-on-global-issues-says-pm/</guid>
      <description>Morning Digest | Look forward to working together on global issues, says PM Modi on Sunak’s elevation; V-Cs can continue till Governor takes decision on show cause notice, says Kerala HC, and more A select list of stories to read before you start your day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian envoy to Kenya meets President Ruto as MEA calls case of missing Indians “very disturbing”</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/indian-envoy-to-kenya-meets-president-ruto-as-mea-calls-case-of-missing-ind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/indian-envoy-to-kenya-meets-president-ruto-as-mea-calls-case-of-missing-ind/</guid>
      <description>Indian envoy to Kenya meets President Ruto as MEA calls case of missing Indians “very disturbing” Kenya arrests the head of disbanded special squad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What of Bitcoin [BTC] when things start getting ‘difficult’</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/what-of-bitcoin-btc-when-things-start-getting-difficult/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/what-of-bitcoin-btc-when-things-start-getting-difficult/</guid>
      <description>What of Bitcoin [BTC] when things start getting ‘difficult’ Bitcoin mining has been subject to a lot of controversies of late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After 5G, here&#39;s how Ambani will use financial services to tighten DNA loop</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/after-5g-heres-how-ambani-will-use-financial-services-to-tighten-dna-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/after-5g-heres-how-ambani-will-use-financial-services-to-tighten-dna-loop/</guid>
      <description>After 5G, here&amp;rsquo;s how Ambani will use financial services to tighten DNA loop A successful fintech loans platform draws upon what the Bank for International Settlements calls a self-reinforcing &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclone Sitrang: IMD issues red alert for four North-East states</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cyclone-sitrang-imd-issues-red-alert-for-four-north-east-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cyclone-sitrang-imd-issues-red-alert-for-four-north-east-states/</guid>
      <description>Cyclone Sitrang: IMD issues red alert for four North-East states In view of the cyclone Sitrang, a red alert indicating heavy to very heavy and extremely heavy rainfall has been issued for Assam, Meghalaya, Mizoram, and Tripura on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asia&#39;s biggest buyout: Toshiba valued at $16 billion by JIP in takeover bid</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/asias-biggest-buyout-toshiba-valued-at-16-billion-by-jip-in-takeover-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/asias-biggest-buyout-toshiba-valued-at-16-billion-by-jip-in-takeover-bid/</guid>
      <description>Asia&amp;rsquo;s biggest buyout: Toshiba valued at $16 billion by JIP in takeover bid A consortium led by Japan Industrial Partners Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Truss reacts after Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin British PM</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/liz-truss-reacts-after-rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-british-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/liz-truss-reacts-after-rishi-sunak-becomes-first-indian-origin-british-pm/</guid>
      <description>Liz Truss reacts after Rishi Sunak becomes first Indian-origin British PM Rishi Sunak, 42, has become Britain&#39;s first Indian-origin Prime Minister after he won the race to lead the Conservative Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak, first Indian-origin UK PM: 10 things to know about him</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-first-indian-origin-uk-pm-10-things-to-know-about-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-first-indian-origin-uk-pm-10-things-to-know-about-him/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak, first Indian-origin UK PM: 10 things to know about him UK PM Race: Rishi Sunak on Monday is all set to make history on Diwali as Britain’s first Indian-origin Prime Minister after being elected unopposed as the new leader of the governing Conservative Party, following Penny Mordaunt&#39;s withdrawal from the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Reddit NFTs’ launch have a positive impact on Polygon’s growth?</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/can-reddit-nfts-launch-have-a-positive-impact-on-polygons-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/can-reddit-nfts-launch-have-a-positive-impact-on-polygons-growth/</guid>
      <description>Can Reddit NFTs’ launch have a positive impact on Polygon’s growth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you should read this before going all in on Tron [TRX]</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/why-you-should-read-this-before-going-all-in-on-tron-trx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/why-you-should-read-this-before-going-all-in-on-tron-trx/</guid>
      <description>Why you should read this before going all in on Tron [TRX] Tron [TRX], the cryptocurrency currently ranked 14th in terms of market cap, was in the news recently for its collaboration with the Dominican government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS’s presence around this liquidity pocket will keep these parties interested</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/eoss-presence-around-this-liquidity-pocket-will-keep-these-parties-inter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/eoss-presence-around-this-liquidity-pocket-will-keep-these-parties-inter/</guid>
      <description>EOS’s presence around this liquidity pocket will keep these parties interested Disclaimer: The information presented does not constitute financial, investment, trading, or other types of advice and is solely the writer’s opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Light: The Spirit of Deepavali</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/guiding-light-the-spirit-of-deepavali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/guiding-light-the-spirit-of-deepavali/</guid>
      <description>Guiding Light: The Spirit of Deepavali Deepavali is our festival of lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theon takes the Golconda St. Leger in style</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/theon-takes-the-golconda-st-leger-in-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/theon-takes-the-golconda-st-leger-in-style/</guid>
      <description>Theon takes the Golconda St. Leger in style thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak set to become U.K.’s first British-Asian Prime Minister</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-set-to-become-uks-first-british-asian-prime-minister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-set-to-become-uks-first-british-asian-prime-minister/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak set to become U.K.’s first British-Asian Prime Minister thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banknotes of Japanese yen and U.S. dollar are seen in this illustration picture taken September 23, 2022. REUTERS/Florence Lo</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/banknotes-of-japanese-yen-and-us-dollar-are-seen-in-this-illustration-pic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/banknotes-of-japanese-yen-and-us-dollar-are-seen-in-this-illustration-pic/</guid>
      <description>Banknotes of Japanese yen and U.S. dollar are seen in this illustration picture taken September 23, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine President Zelenskyy says Russia ordered some 2,000 drones from Iran</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ukraine-president-zelenskyy-says-russia-ordered-some-2000-drones-from-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ukraine-president-zelenskyy-says-russia-ordered-some-2000-drones-from-iran/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine President Zelenskyy says Russia ordered some 2,000 drones from Iran According to Ukrainian intelligence, Russia ordered about 2,000 &#39;Shaheds&#39; from Iran</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britain&#39;s Conservative MP Rishi Sunak walks next to his campaign headquarters in London, Britain, October 24, 2022. REUTERS/Hannah McKay</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/britains-conservative-mp-rishi-sunak-walks-next-to-his-campaign-headquarte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/britains-conservative-mp-rishi-sunak-walks-next-to-his-campaign-headquarte/</guid>
      <description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Conservative MP Rishi Sunak walks next to his campaign headquarters in London, Britain, October 24, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karnataka SHOCKER: Cop charged for allegedly raping cousin over 5 years- Details here</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karnataka-shocker-cop-charged-for-allegedly-raping-cousin-over-5-years-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karnataka-shocker-cop-charged-for-allegedly-raping-cousin-over-5-years-de/</guid>
      <description>Karnataka SHOCKER: Cop charged for allegedly raping cousin over 5 years- Details here The survivor said when she went to meet Umesh on September 13, 2017, he raped her and threatened her not to tell this to anyone or else he will make her family&#39;s life miserable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As &#39;Punjabi-Munda&#39; Rishi Sunak wins UK PM race, desis&#39; chest swell with pride. Read reax here</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/as-punjabi-munda-rishi-sunak-wins-uk-pm-race-desis-chest-swell-with-pri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/as-punjabi-munda-rishi-sunak-wins-uk-pm-race-desis-chest-swell-with-pri/</guid>
      <description>As &amp;lsquo;Punjabi-Munda&amp;rsquo; Rishi Sunak wins UK PM race, desis&#39; chest swell with pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New leader of Britain&#39;s Conservative Party Rishi Sunak stands outside the party&#39;s headquarters in London, Britain, October 24, 2022. REUTERS/Henry Nicholls</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/new-leader-of-britains-conservative-party-rishi-sunak-stands-outside-the-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/new-leader-of-britains-conservative-party-rishi-sunak-stands-outside-the-p/</guid>
      <description>New leader of Britain&amp;rsquo;s Conservative Party Rishi Sunak stands outside the party&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in London, Britain, October 24, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Pakistan PM Imran Khan can contest elections: Islamabad High Court</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ousted-pakistan-pm-imran-khan-can-contest-elections-islamabad-high-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ousted-pakistan-pm-imran-khan-can-contest-elections-islamabad-high-court/</guid>
      <description>Ousted Pakistan PM Imran Khan can contest elections: Islamabad High Court The Court would hear the petition once the objections were removed, the judge said as he also refused to issue a stay order on the ECP verdict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karman Thandi wins $60,000 event, becomes India No.1</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karman-thandi-wins-60000-event-becomes-india-no1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/karman-thandi-wins-60000-event-becomes-india-no1/</guid>
      <description>Karman Thandi wins $60,000 event, becomes India No.1 Karman had enjoyed a career-best rank of 196 in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaniard Santiago Sánchez Trekking to Qatar for FIFA World Cup 2022 Reported Missing in Iran</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/spaniard-santiago-snchez-trekking-to-qatar-for-fifa-world-cup-2022-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/spaniard-santiago-snchez-trekking-to-qatar-for-fifa-world-cup-2022-report/</guid>
      <description>Spaniard Santiago Sánchez Trekking to Qatar for FIFA World Cup 2022 Reported Missing in Iran Sánchez&#39;s reported disappearance in Iran, his last stop before reaching Qatar for the World Cup, comes as protesters rise up across the Islamic Republic in the largest antigovernment movement in over a decade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengaluru: बायोकॉन प्रमुख किरण मजूमदार शॉ के पति जॉन शॉ का निधन, लंबे समय से थे बीमार</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/kiran-mazumdar-shaw-s-husband-john-shaw-died-in-bengaluru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/kiran-mazumdar-shaw-s-husband-john-shaw-died-in-bengaluru/</guid>
      <description>Bengaluru: बायोकॉन प्रमुख किरण मजूमदार शॉ के पति जॉन शॉ का निधन, लंबे समय से थे बीमार Kiran Mazumdar Shaw&#39;s Husband Death: बायोकॉन की कार्यकारी चेयरपर्सन किरण मजूमदार शॉ (Kiran Mazumdar Shaw) के पति जॉन शॉ (John Shaw) का सोमवार (24 अक्टूबर) सुबह एक निजी अस्पताल में निधन हो गया.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian- Origin Rishi Sunak Set to Take the Top Job of UK&#39;s PM</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/indian-origin-rishi-sunak-set-to-take-the-top-job-of-uks-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/indian-origin-rishi-sunak-set-to-take-the-top-job-of-uks-pm/</guid>
      <description>Indian- Origin Rishi Sunak Set to Take the Top Job of UK&amp;rsquo;s PM At age 42, he will be the youngest and the first non- white person to hold the post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notice Asking Women Advocates To Stop &#39;Arranging Hair In Open Court&#39; Causes Uproar</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/notice-asking-women-advocates-to-stop-arranging-hair-in-open-court-causes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/notice-asking-women-advocates-to-stop-arranging-hair-in-open-court-causes/</guid>
      <description>Notice Asking Women Advocates To Stop &amp;lsquo;Arranging Hair In Open Court&amp;rsquo; Causes Uproar It is regularly seen that women advocates are styling their hair in open Court, which is disrupting the running of the Court,&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miya Museum in Goalpara Sparks Sharp Reactions</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/miya-museum-in-goalpara-sparks-sharp-reactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/miya-museum-in-goalpara-sparks-sharp-reactions/</guid>
      <description>Miya Museum in Goalpara Sparks Sharp Reactions The Goalpara Committee of the All Assam Miya Parisad inaugurated a Miya Museum in Gopalpara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Startup that is Changing the Paradigm of Travel</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/a-startup-that-is-changing-the-paradigm-of-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/a-startup-that-is-changing-the-paradigm-of-travel/</guid>
      <description>A Startup that is Changing the Paradigm of Travel Oddessemania is a travel tech startup that is trying to change the way people experience travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaastu Rules for Windows and Staircases</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/vaastu-rules-for-windows-and-staircases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/vaastu-rules-for-windows-and-staircases/</guid>
      <description>Vaastu Rules for Windows and Staircases The number of windows in a house should always be even like 4, 6, 8, 10 etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tirumala temple to remain closed tomorrow due to Solar ecclipse</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/tirumala-temple-to-remain-closed-tomorrow-due-to-solar-ecclipse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/tirumala-temple-to-remain-closed-tomorrow-due-to-solar-ecclipse/</guid>
      <description>Tirumala temple to remain closed tomorrow due to Solar ecclipse The Tirumala Tirupati Devasthanam announced that Tirumala temple will be closed on Tuesday from 8 am to 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NPCI Recruitment 2022 - Incharge Loyalty Vacancy, Latest Job Openings</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/npci-recruitment-2022-incharge-loyalty-vacancy-latest-job-openings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/npci-recruitment-2022-incharge-loyalty-vacancy-latest-job-openings/</guid>
      <description>NPCI Recruitment 2022 - Incharge Loyalty Vacancy, Latest Job Openings National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) invites candidates for the post of Incharge Loyalty Jobs in India, Apply Now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hug your Way to a Healthy and Happy Life</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/hug-your-way-to-a-healthy-and-happy-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/hug-your-way-to-a-healthy-and-happy-life/</guid>
      <description>Hug your Way to a Healthy and Happy Life The simple action of embracing creates feel-good energy for both the giver and recipient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: PM Modi sings &#39;Maa Tujhe Salaam&#39; along with soliders at Kargil on Diwali- WATCH</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/video-pm-modi-sings-maa-tujhe-salaam-along-with-soliders-at-kargil-on-di/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/video-pm-modi-sings-maa-tujhe-salaam-along-with-soliders-at-kargil-on-di/</guid>
      <description>Video: PM Modi sings &amp;lsquo;Maa Tujhe Salaam&amp;rsquo; along with soliders at Kargil on Diwali- WATCH He also laid a wreath at the Kargil War Memorial and paid tribute to the army personnel who lost their lives here in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toddler attacked, killed by leopard at Mumbai’s Aarey colony</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/toddler-attacked-killed-by-leopard-at-mumbais-aarey-colony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/toddler-attacked-killed-by-leopard-at-mumbais-aarey-colony/</guid>
      <description>Toddler attacked, killed by leopard at Mumbai’s Aarey colony A leopard attacked the girl and injured her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jury selection set to begin Trump company&#39;s criminal tax trial today</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jury-selection-set-to-begin-trump-companys-criminal-tax-trial-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jury-selection-set-to-begin-trump-companys-criminal-tax-trial-today/</guid>
      <description>Jury selection set to begin Trump company&amp;rsquo;s criminal tax trial today Prosecutors in Manhattan accused Trump’s real estate business of defrauding tax authorities to company executives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinance to hike quota for SC/STs gets Governor’s assent</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ordinance-to-hike-quota-for-scsts-gets-governors-assent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ordinance-to-hike-quota-for-scsts-gets-governors-assent/</guid>
      <description>Ordinance to hike quota for SC/STs gets Governor’s assent thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newcastle beat Tottenham to move into Premier League top four</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/newcastle-beat-tottenham-to-move-into-premier-league-top-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/newcastle-beat-tottenham-to-move-into-premier-league-top-four/</guid>
      <description>Newcastle beat Tottenham to move into Premier League top four Callum Wilson and Miguel Almiron were on target for the Magpies, who have still only lost once this season</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explained | CCI’s ₹1,300 crore fine on Google and how that will change Android smartphones</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/explained-ccis-1300-crore-fine-on-google-and-how-that-will-change-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/explained-ccis-1300-crore-fine-on-google-and-how-that-will-change-/</guid>
      <description>Explained | CCI’s ₹1,300 crore fine on Google and how that will change Android smartphones How is the Alphabet owned company allegedly violating its position especially with regard to the Android mobile device ecosystem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;BJP&#39;s Sambit Patra, Iqbal Singh Lalpura violating Central Civil Services rules&#39;: AAP</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bjps-sambit-patra-iqbal-singh-lalpura-violating-central-civil-services-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bjps-sambit-patra-iqbal-singh-lalpura-violating-central-civil-services-r/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;BJP&amp;rsquo;s Sambit Patra, Iqbal Singh Lalpura violating Central Civil Services rules&amp;rsquo;: AAP Patra and Lalpura did not respond immediately to the AAP&#39;s demand for their removal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two mediapersons among six arrested for ‘extorting’ ₹1.2 lakh from a businessman in Visakhapatnam</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/two-mediapersons-among-six-arrested-for-extorting-12-lakh-from-a-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/two-mediapersons-among-six-arrested-for-extorting-12-lakh-from-a-/</guid>
      <description>Two mediapersons among six arrested for ‘extorting’ ₹1.2 lakh from a businessman in Visakhapatnam The city police arrested six persons, including two mediapersons, for allegedly threatening and extorting ₹1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newly married teacher found dead</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/newly-married-teacher-found-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/newly-married-teacher-found-dead/</guid>
      <description>Newly married teacher found dead A 25-year-old newly married private school teacher was found dead under mysterious circumstances at her apartment in Puttenahalli on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat: PM Narendra Modi’s meet with Patidar leader sets tongues wagging</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/gujarat-pm-narendra-modis-meet-with-patidar-leader-sets-tongues-wagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/gujarat-pm-narendra-modis-meet-with-patidar-leader-sets-tongues-wagging/</guid>
      <description>Gujarat: PM Narendra Modi’s meet with Patidar leader sets tongues wagging Ahmedabad: Amid speculation that Prime Minister Narendra Modi may visit influential Patidar organisations on Sardar Patel’s birth anniversary on October 31 in a renewed bid to win over the community, Naresh Patel, Chairman of the Shree Khodaldham Trust, met him at his residence in New Delhi on Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jagan to launch third 800-MW unit of supercritical thermal power plant in Andhra Pradesh on October 27</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jagan-to-launch-third-800-mw-unit-of-supercritical-thermal-power-plant-in-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/jagan-to-launch-third-800-mw-unit-of-supercritical-thermal-power-plant-in-a/</guid>
      <description>Jagan to launch third 800-MW unit of supercritical thermal power plant in Andhra Pradesh on October 27 The Chief Minister to also disburse non-fishermen package to the displaced people pending since former Chief Minister Rajasekhara Reddy’s term</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andhra Pradesh: Sankar Foundation to conduct mega eye camp to mark Swaroopanandendra Swami’s birthday on October 28</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/andhra-pradesh-sankar-foundation-to-conduct-mega-eye-camp-to-mark-swaroopa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/andhra-pradesh-sankar-foundation-to-conduct-mega-eye-camp-to-mark-swaroopa/</guid>
      <description>Andhra Pradesh: Sankar Foundation to conduct mega eye camp to mark Swaroopanandendra Swami’s birthday on October 28 thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart garbage monitoring app for Thrikkakara too</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/smart-garbage-monitoring-app-for-thrikkakara-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/smart-garbage-monitoring-app-for-thrikkakara-too/</guid>
      <description>Smart garbage monitoring app for Thrikkakara too thehindu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring Ernakulam-Angamaly archdiocese under direct administration of Pope, demands laity group</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bring-ernakulam-angamaly-archdiocese-under-direct-administration-of-pope-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 12:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bring-ernakulam-angamaly-archdiocese-under-direct-administration-of-pope-d/</guid>
      <description>Bring Ernakulam-Angamaly archdiocese under direct administration of Pope, demands laity group Group says lay people and priests have lost faith in the Syro-Malabar Church leadership</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP Will Retain Power In Himachal Pradesh: Anurag Thakur</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bjp-will-retain-power-in-himachal-pradesh-anurag-thakur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/bjp-will-retain-power-in-himachal-pradesh-anurag-thakur/</guid>
      <description>BJP Will Retain Power In Himachal Pradesh: Anurag Thakur Targeting the Aam Aadmi Party, Thakur said the Kejriwal-led outfit will not be able to open an account in the Himachal Pradesh Assembly elections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
