<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>health on NewsStreet | News from several media houses</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in health on NewsStreet | News from several media houses</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reasons why you should never skip breakfast</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/reasons-why-you-should-never-skip-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/reasons-why-you-should-never-skip-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Reasons why you should never skip breakfast IANSlife New Delhi, October 24 What is the first thing that concerns most people immediately after waking up in the morning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwali 2022: Tips to maintain safety and health during the festival</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/diwali-2022-tips-to-maintain-safety-and-health-during-the-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/diwali-2022-tips-to-maintain-safety-and-health-during-the-festival/</guid>
      <description>Diwali 2022: Tips to maintain safety and health during the festival Diwali is a festival which is full of our energy and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety disorders had no effect on vaccine hesitancy</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/anxiety-disorders-had-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/anxiety-disorders-had-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy/</guid>
      <description>Anxiety disorders had no effect on vaccine hesitancy These findings help shed light on the best way for the government to promote vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety disorder has no effect on vaccine hesitancy: Study</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/anxiety-disorder-has-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/anxiety-disorder-has-no-effect-on-vaccine-hesitancy-study/</guid>
      <description>Anxiety disorder has no effect on vaccine hesitancy: Study IANS New Delhi, October 24 Individuals who deal with anxiety are no less hesitant to get the Covid-19 vaccine compared to those without anxiety, according to new research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy protects infants from SARS-CoV-2 infection</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/covid-19-vaccination-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-from-sars-cov-2-infe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/covid-19-vaccination-during-pregnancy-protects-infants-from-sars-cov-2-infe/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 vaccination during pregnancy protects infants from SARS-CoV-2 infection In a recent study under review at the Nature Portfolio journal and currently posted to Research Square* preprint server, researchers evaluated the efficacy of maternal coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) vaccination against infection of infants with severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A novel approach for viral genomic surveillance</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/a-novel-approach-for-viral-genomic-surveillance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/a-novel-approach-for-viral-genomic-surveillance/</guid>
      <description>A novel approach for viral genomic surveillance In a recent study posted to the bioRxiv* preprint server, researchers in the United States explored a novel technique to improve representation in viral genomic surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antibody-mediated protection against symptomatic COVID achieved at low serum neutralizing titers</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/antibody-mediated-protection-against-symptomatic-covid-achieved-at-low-seru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/antibody-mediated-protection-against-symptomatic-covid-achieved-at-low-seru/</guid>
      <description>Antibody-mediated protection against symptomatic COVID achieved at low serum neutralizing titers In a recent study posted to the medRxiv* preprint server, researchers in the United States assessed the efficiency of protection mediated by antibodies against symptomatic coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) at low serum-neutralizing titers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>डिलीवरी के बाद होने वाली सामान्य समस्याएं, महिलाएं इनके बारे में जरूर जान लें</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/-/</guid>
      <description>डिलीवरी के बाद होने वाली सामान्य समस्याएं, महिलाएं इनके बारे में जरूर जान लें Postpartum Problems- महिलाओं को डिलीवरी के कुछ समय बाद तक दर्द, परेशानी और थकावट महसूस होना आम है, लेकिन लंबे समय तक परेशानी का सामना करने के बजाय डॉक्टर से परामर्श करना जरूरी है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research suggests that ORF6 is a major SARS-CoV-2 innate immune antagonist</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/research-suggests-that-orf6-is-a-major-sars-cov-2-innate-immune-antagonist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/research-suggests-that-orf6-is-a-major-sars-cov-2-innate-immune-antagonist/</guid>
      <description>Research suggests that ORF6 is a major SARS-CoV-2 innate immune antagonist In a recent study posted to the bioRxiv* server, researchers in the United States demonstrated how severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) open reading frame 6 (ORF6) protein contributes to viral pathogenesis and modulates the host&#39;s immune responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Nations Day: आज है यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे, जानें क्या है इस बार की थीम और इसकी हिस्ट्री</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/united-nations-day-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 03:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/united-nations-day-/</guid>
      <description>United Nations Day: आज है यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे, जानें क्या है इस बार की थीम और इसकी हिस्ट्री United Nations day-October 24- हर साल 24 अक्टूबर को यूनाइटेड नेशंस डे मनाया जाता है और इस दिन ही यूनाइटेड नेशन को ऑफिशियल रूप से स्थापित किया गया था.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
