<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basketball on NewsStreet | News portal</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/basketball/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basketball on NewsStreet | News portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:30:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/basketball/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>“We’re Out of the LeBron James Era”: When Kevin Garnett Ranked Stephen Curry Over LBJ, Credited Warriors Star for Changing NBA</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/were-out-of-the-lebron-james-era-when-kevin-garnett-ranked-stephe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/were-out-of-the-lebron-james-era-when-kevin-garnett-ranked-stephe/</guid>
      <description>“We’re Out of the LeBron James Era”: When Kevin Garnett Ranked Stephen Curry Over LBJ, Credited Warriors Star for Changing NBA Koven Garnett, who was an enforcer for the Boston Celtics, claimed that LeBron James’ era was overtaken by Stephen Curry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once Termed ‘Tragic’, Magic Johnson Offers ‘Accountability’ Advice to Russell Westbrook Post Lakers 0-3 Start</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/once-termed-tragic-magic-johnson-offers-accountability-advice-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/once-termed-tragic-magic-johnson-offers-accountability-advice-/</guid>
      <description>Once Termed ‘Tragic’, Magic Johnson Offers ‘Accountability’ Advice to Russell Westbrook Post Lakers 0-3 Start Lakers legend Magic Johnson imparts advice to Russell Westbrook while citing his example of being called Tragic Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“He Did but he was Just There as Father Figure”: Kobe Bryant Reveals Father Joe Bryant’s Contribution to NBA Career</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/he-did-but-he-was-just-there-as-father-figure-kobe-bryant-reveals-fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/he-did-but-he-was-just-there-as-father-figure-kobe-bryant-reveals-fa/</guid>
      <description>“He Did but he was Just There as Father Figure”: Kobe Bryant Reveals Father Joe Bryant’s Contribution to NBA Career Kobe Bryant is a prodigious talent and his accolades are directly accredited to his upbringing, with Joe Bryant, his dad, an integral figure!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Never Seen That Before”: Andre Iguodala Was Flabbergasted By Stephen Curry’s Turn Around 3 Pointer During the 2013 Playoffs</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/never-seen-that-before-andre-iguodala-was-flabbergasted-by-stephen-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/never-seen-that-before-andre-iguodala-was-flabbergasted-by-stephen-c/</guid>
      <description>“Never Seen That Before”: Andre Iguodala Was Flabbergasted By Stephen Curry’s Turn Around 3 Pointer During the 2013 Playoffs Stephen Curry averaged a staggering 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaquille O’Neal Was Once Told to Help the Less Fortunate By His Father, Phillip Harrison, After a Trip to White Castle</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/shaquille-oneal-was-once-told-to-help-the-less-fortunate-by-his-father-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/shaquille-oneal-was-once-told-to-help-the-less-fortunate-by-his-father-/</guid>
      <description>Shaquille O’Neal Was Once Told to Help the Less Fortunate By His Father, Phillip Harrison, After a Trip to White Castle Most children learn valuable lessons from their parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“I’m The Only Player in NBA History To Build An Image Without Nike or Adidas”: Dennis Rodman Once Boasted About the Sheer Uniqueness of his Eccentricity</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/im-the-only-player-in-nba-history-to-build-an-image-without-nike-or-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/im-the-only-player-in-nba-history-to-build-an-image-without-nike-or-a/</guid>
      <description>“I’m The Only Player in NBA History To Build An Image Without Nike or Adidas”: Dennis Rodman Once Boasted About the Sheer Uniqueness of his Eccentricity Dennis Rodman is one of the most polarising figures in basketball lore, but claims to be the first sportsman with an entirely self-made image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Dwight Howard Was Better and More Athletic Than Me”: Shaquille O’Neal Expresses Disappointment Over Ex-Laker’s Dismissal of His Advice</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dwight-howard-was-better-and-more-athletic-than-me-shaquille-onea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dwight-howard-was-better-and-more-athletic-than-me-shaquille-onea/</guid>
      <description>“Dwight Howard Was Better and More Athletic Than Me”: Shaquille O’Neal Expresses Disappointment Over Ex-Laker’s Dismissal of His Advice Dwight Howard was in more ways than one a successor to Shaquille O’Neal – He had all the tools to become an all-time great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“No Clutch Gene”: Skip Bayless Attacks LeBron James After Lakers Lose Three Consecutive Games</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/no-clutch-gene-skip-bayless-attacks-lebron-james-after-lakers-lose-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/no-clutch-gene-skip-bayless-attacks-lebron-james-after-lakers-lose-t/</guid>
      <description>“No Clutch Gene”: Skip Bayless Attacks LeBron James After Lakers Lose Three Consecutive Games Skip Bayless, who is an ardent Michael Jordan fan, has targeted LeBron James again after the Los Angeles Lakers’ third consecutive loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Paolo Banchero Playing Tonight vs Knicks? Orlando Magic Release Injury Report on Rookie </title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/is-paolo-banchero-playing-tonight-vs-knicks-orlando-magic-release-injury-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/is-paolo-banchero-playing-tonight-vs-knicks-orlando-magic-release-injury-r/</guid>
      <description>Is Paolo Banchero Playing Tonight vs Knicks? Orlando Magic Release Injury Report on Rookie  Paolo Banchero is the name on everyone’s mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“I’m Not Worried About Money at This Stage of my Life”: Charles Barkley Reveals Exquisite Details of Meeting with Turner Post Signing Potential $200 Million Deal</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/im-not-worried-about-money-at-this-stage-of-my-life-charles-barkl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/im-not-worried-about-money-at-this-stage-of-my-life-charles-barkl/</guid>
      <description>“I’m Not Worried About Money at This Stage of my Life”: Charles Barkley Reveals Exquisite Details of Meeting with Turner Post Signing Potential $200 Million Deal NBA Hall of Famer Charles Barkley explains at length what got him to sign a 10-year contract with TNT that could fetch him close to $200 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Zion Williamson Playing Tonight vs Jazz? NOLA Issues Availability Report for 6-foot-6 Forward Ahead of Clash in Home Opener</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/is-zion-williamson-playing-tonight-vs-jazz-nola-issues-availability-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/is-zion-williamson-playing-tonight-vs-jazz-nola-issues-availability-report/</guid>
      <description>Is Zion Williamson Playing Tonight vs Jazz? NOLA Issues Availability Report for 6-foot-6 Forward Ahead of Clash in Home Opener Zion Williamson will play a huge role in helping the New Orleans Pelicans grab a win in their home opener on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
