<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on NewsStreet | News from several media houses</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on NewsStreet | News from several media houses</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 19:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/did-nato-plan-a-pre-emptive-strike-on-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 19:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/did-nato-plan-a-pre-emptive-strike-on-russia/</guid>
      <description>Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia Polaris 21 - The French Maritime Exercise that saw participation of 24 ships, one submarine, 65 aircraft and 6000 personnel with partners from Europe and USA The post Did NATO Plan A Pre-Emptive Strike On Russia appeared first on N4M (News4masses).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP objects to massive crowd during Vikramaditya Singh’s nomination, approaches ECI</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/bjp-objects-to-massive-crowd-during-vikramaditya-singhs-nomination-appr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/bjp-objects-to-massive-crowd-during-vikramaditya-singhs-nomination-appr/</guid>
      <description>BJP objects to massive crowd during Vikramaditya Singh’s nomination, approaches ECI Shimla: Irked over witnessing a massive crowd during the nomination of former six-time Chief Minister Virbhadra Singh and MLA Vikramaditya Singh has made Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), the party has approached the election commission and has filed a complaint against Singh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonia, Rahul, Kharge on list of 40-star campaigners for Himachal poll</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/sonia-rahul-kharge-on-list-of-40-star-campaigners-for-himachal-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 16:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/sonia-rahul-kharge-on-list-of-40-star-campaigners-for-himachal-poll/</guid>
      <description>Sonia, Rahul, Kharge on list of 40-star campaigners for Himachal poll Shimla: Newly elected President of the All India Congress Committee (AICC), Mallikarjun Kharge, former Presidents Rahul Gandhi and Sonia Gandhi and Congress General Secretary Priyanka Gandhi Vadra will be the star campaigners of Congress in the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress fields Jagat from Kinnaur, Gaur from Manali</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/congress-fields-jagat-from-kinnaur-gaur-from-manali/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/blog/congress-fields-jagat-from-kinnaur-gaur-from-manali/</guid>
      <description>Congress fields Jagat from Kinnaur, Gaur from Manali Shimla: Indian National Congress has issued its third list of candidates for four Legislative Assembly Constituencies and once again has fielded four-time MLA Jagat Singh Negi (ST) as its candidate from Kinnaur.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
