<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NE News,Assam News on NewsStreet | News portal</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/ne-newsassam-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NE News,Assam News on NewsStreet | News portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:16:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/tags/ne-newsassam-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cancer awareness programme on the use of tobacco held in Assam&#39;s Lakhimpur</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cancer-awareness-programme-on-the-use-of-tobacco-held-in-assams-lakhimpur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 10:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cancer-awareness-programme-on-the-use-of-tobacco-held-in-assams-lakhimpur/</guid>
      <description>Cancer awareness programme on the use of tobacco held in Assam&amp;rsquo;s Lakhimpur In association with Assam Cancer Care Foundation (ACCF), organized an awareness programme on the use of tobacco and its relation with cancer and breast cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheques given to 4,668 Micro-Finance Incentive and Relief Scheme (AMFIRS) borrowers in Dhemaji district</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cheques-given-to-4668-micro-finance-incentive-and-relief-scheme-amfirs-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 09:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/cheques-given-to-4668-micro-finance-incentive-and-relief-scheme-amfirs-b/</guid>
      <description>Cheques given to 4,668 Micro-Finance Incentive and Relief Scheme (AMFIRS) borrowers in Dhemaji district The distribution of the cheques under the AMFIRS - 2021-2022, Category-II was formally inaugurated by Sanjay Kishan, the Minister for Tea Tribes and Labour Welfare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series of activities for cleaning and disposal matters conducted in Krishi Vigyan Kendra (KVK) Dibrugarh</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/series-of-activities-for-cleaning-and-disposal-matters-conducted-in-krishi-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/series-of-activities-for-cleaning-and-disposal-matters-conducted-in-krishi-/</guid>
      <description>Series of activities for cleaning and disposal matters conducted in Krishi Vigyan Kendra (KVK) Dibrugarh The main aim is to create a good work environment and work efficiently for the greater interest of delivering good services to public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orientation programme on National Education Policy 2020 held at Assam&#39;s Biswanath College of Education</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/orientation-programme-on-national-education-policy-2020-held-at-assams-bis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 07:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/orientation-programme-on-national-education-policy-2020-held-at-assams-bis/</guid>
      <description>Orientation programme on National Education Policy 2020 held at Assam&amp;rsquo;s Biswanath College of Education The programme was hosted by A Handique, coordinator of CTEF, Biswanath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Assamese cine artiste Nipon Goswami&#39;s death condoled</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/legendary-assamese-cine-artiste-nipon-goswamis-death-condoled/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/legendary-assamese-cine-artiste-nipon-goswamis-death-condoled/</guid>
      <description>Legendary Assamese cine artiste Nipon Goswami&amp;rsquo;s death condoled ANSS, in a press statement issued by Durga Khatiara, president, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vermicompost from banana leaves in Krishi Vigyan Kendra, Tinsukia</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/vermicompost-from-banana-leaves-in-krishi-vigyan-kendra-tinsukia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/vermicompost-from-banana-leaves-in-krishi-vigyan-kendra-tinsukia/</guid>
      <description>Vermicompost from banana leaves in Krishi Vigyan Kendra, Tinsukia KVK, Tinsukia as a part of Swachhata Campaign under SAP initiated a novel plan to recycle banana leaves for manufacturing of vermicompost during post-Diwali days at the kendra’s production unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businessman shot at by miscreants in Udalguri district</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/businessman-shot-at-by-miscreants-in-udalguri-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/businessman-shot-at-by-miscreants-in-udalguri-district/</guid>
      <description>Businessman shot at by miscreants in Udalguri district Amidst the Diwali celebration, unidentified masked miscreants shot businessman Gautam Baruah and his wife Bobita Baruah at the latter&#39;s residence in the Jalukbari locality of Tangla town</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAC election: 19 candidates to contest in 5 constituencies of Dhemaji</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dac-election-19-candidates-to-contest-in-5-constituencies-of-dhemaji/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/dac-election-19-candidates-to-contest-in-5-constituencies-of-dhemaji/</guid>
      <description>DAC election: 19 candidates to contest in 5 constituencies of Dhemaji With October 25 being the last date for the withdrawal of the nomination papers for the Deori Autonomous Council (DAC) Election, 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACS candidates felicitated in Mangaldai</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/acs-candidates-felicitated-in-mangaldai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/acs-candidates-felicitated-in-mangaldai/</guid>
      <description>ACS candidates felicitated in Mangaldai Various social organizations of Mangaldai including the premier media organization, MMC have greeted and congratulated Dr Jebin Gulnar, the 3rd rank holder in the ACS examination results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overflowing water submerges villages under Kampur revenue circle</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/overflowing-water-submerges-villages-under-kampur-revenue-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 06:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/overflowing-water-submerges-villages-under-kampur-revenue-circle/</guid>
      <description>Overflowing water submerges villages under Kampur revenue circle Due to the incessant rains across the State, Karbi Langpi Hydro Electric Power Project released additional water through four sluice gates of the big dam of the power project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/9-youths-of-sonitpur-bring-laurels-by-clearing-apsc-exam/</guid>
      <description>9 youths of Sonitpur bring laurels by clearing APSC exam A total of nine candidates in the Sonitpur district have brought laurels to the district by achieving different ranks in the recently declared results of the APSC CCE 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
