<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>world on NewsStreet | News portal</title>
    <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in world on NewsStreet | News portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:27:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newsstreet.github.io/categories/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>India will not forget 26/11 attack on Mumbai: Jaishankar at UNSC meet on terrorism</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/india-will-not-forget-2611-attack-on-mumbai-jaishankar-at-unsc-meet-on-te/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/india-will-not-forget-2611-attack-on-mumbai-jaishankar-at-unsc-meet-on-te/</guid>
      <description>India will not forget 26/11 attack on Mumbai: Jaishankar at UNSC meet on terrorism India will not forget 26/11 attack on Mumbai: Jaishankar at UNSC meet on terrorism</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From flamethrowers to challenging Putin to combat, why Elon Musk is the king of publicity stunts</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/from-flamethrowers-to-challenging-putin-to-combat-why-elon-musk-is-the-kin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/from-flamethrowers-to-challenging-putin-to-combat-why-elon-musk-is-the-kin/</guid>
      <description>From flamethrowers to challenging Putin to combat, why Elon Musk is the king of publicity stunts From flamethrowers to challenging Putin to combat, why Elon Musk is the king of publicity stunts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>अमेरिका के ​​एरिया-51 में बसी है रहस्यमय दुनिया, हथियारों की टेस्टिंग का बेस या एलियन अड्डा? जानें</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/area-51-secret-area-51-ka-rahasya-area-51-kya-hai-full-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/area-51-secret-area-51-ka-rahasya-area-51-kya-hai-full-detail/</guid>
      <description>अमेरिका के ​​एरिया-51 में बसी है रहस्यमय दुनिया, हथियारों की टेस्टिंग का बेस या एलियन अड्डा?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson tried to make a comeback. And people were just going to let him.</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/boris-johnson-tried-to-make-a-comeback-and-people-were-just-going-to-let-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/boris-johnson-tried-to-make-a-comeback-and-people-were-just-going-to-let-h/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson tried to make a comeback. And people were just going to let him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak becomes UK’s first Indian-origin prime minister</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-becomes-uks-first-indian-origin-prime-minister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/rishi-sunak-becomes-uks-first-indian-origin-prime-minister/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak becomes UK’s first Indian-origin prime minister London, Oct 24: Indian-origin Rishi Sunak was named the next prime minister of the United Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imran Khan: इमरान खान को इस्लामाबाद हाईकोर्ट से भी झटका, पाकिस्तान चुनाव आयोग के फैसले के खिलाफ याचिका खारिज</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/imran-khan-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 08:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/imran-khan-/</guid>
      <description>Imran Khan: इमरान खान को इस्लामाबाद हाईकोर्ट से भी झटका, पाकिस्तान चुनाव आयोग के फैसले के खिलाफ याचिका खारिज Imran Khan News: इस्लामाबाद हाई कोर्ट (Islamabad High Court) ने पूर्व पीएम इमरान खान (Imran Khan) की याचिका को खारिज कर दिया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Governor celebrates Diwali with Indian-Americans</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/texas-governor-celebrates-diwali-with-indian-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/texas-governor-celebrates-diwali-with-indian-americans/</guid>
      <description>Texas Governor celebrates Diwali with Indian-Americans The couple was dressed in ethnic Indian attire as they welcomed guests, and also lit the traditional lamp to mark the festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shahed-136 Drone: यूक्रेन में हमला करने के लिए रूस Shahed-136 ड्रोन का इस्तेमाल लगातार कर रहा है-UK</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/shahed-136-drone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/shahed-136-drone-/</guid>
      <description>Shahed-136 Drone: यूक्रेन में हमला करने के लिए रूस Shahed-136 ड्रोन का इस्तेमाल लगातार कर रहा है-UK सात माह से अध‍िक समय से जारी रूस और यूक्रेन की जंग के बीच अब Shahed-136 ड्रोन चर्चा में है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He went to the room and knocked and called but there was no response; Expatriate Malayali died in Saudi</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/he-went-to-the-room-and-knocked-and-called-but-there-was-no-response-expat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/he-went-to-the-room-and-knocked-and-called-but-there-was-no-response-expat/</guid>
      <description>He went to the room and knocked and called but there was no response; Expatriate Malayali died in Saudi Saudi: Ajit Sahadevan, a native of Kanyakumari Moovotukonam, who was working at Riyadh Exit 7 Alwadi, died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iran Cyber Attack:महासा अमिनी की मौत पर मचे बवाल के बीच ईरान के परमाणु ऊर्जा एजेंसी पर साइबर अटैक से हड़कंप, विदेशी साजिश का आरोप</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/iran-cyber-attack-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/iran-cyber-attack-/</guid>
      <description>Iran Cyber Attack:महासा अमिनी की मौत पर मचे बवाल के बीच ईरान के परमाणु ऊर्जा एजेंसी पर साइबर अटैक से हड़कंप, विदेशी साजिश का आरोप Cyber Attack On Iran Nuclear Energy Agency: हैकर्स दुनिया की बड़ी एजेंसियों को अपना निशाना बना रहे हैं.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice engineering laboratory to be created in the Jewish Autonomous Region</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ice-engineering-laboratory-to-be-created-in-the-jewish-autonomous-region/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/ice-engineering-laboratory-to-be-created-in-the-jewish-autonomous-region/</guid>
      <description>Ice engineering laboratory to be created in the Jewish Autonomous Region The JAO plans to develop effective ways to destroy the ice cover on rivers during freeze-up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow almost a quarter of the sun will be eclipsed: ‘Pretty good chance of good visibility’</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/tomorrow-almost-a-quarter-of-the-sun-will-be-eclipsed-pretty-good-chanc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/tomorrow-almost-a-quarter-of-the-sun-will-be-eclipsed-pretty-good-chanc/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow almost a quarter of the sun will be eclipsed: ‘Pretty good chance of good visibility’ There is a good chance that we will be able to see part of the solar eclipse tomorrow in the Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>पाकिस्तानी पत्रकार अरशद शरीफ की केन्या में गोली मारकर हत्या, PM शहबाज शरीफ ने जताया दुख</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pakistan-arshad-sharif-killed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pakistan-arshad-sharif-killed/</guid>
      <description>पाकिस्तानी पत्रकार अरशद शरीफ की केन्या में गोली मारकर हत्या, PM शहबाज शरीफ ने जताया दुख Arshad Sharif Killed: पाकिस्तान के वरिष्ठ पत्रकार अरशद शरीफ की केन्या (Kenya) के नैरोबी (Nairobi) शहर में कथित तौर पर गोली लगने से मौत हो गई.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Iran to Azerbaijan, 84 Hyderabads: पूरी दुनिया में एक या दो नहीं, कुल 84 हैदराबाद हैं</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/from-iran-to-azerbaijan-84-hyderabads-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/from-iran-to-azerbaijan-84-hyderabads-/</guid>
      <description>From Iran to Azerbaijan, 84 Hyderabads: पूरी दुनिया में एक या दो नहीं, कुल 84 हैदराबाद हैं हैदराबाद जिसे शहर-ए-निगाराँ कहिए रंग-ए-रुख़्सार सहर-ए-हुस्न-ए-बहाराँ कहिए उस के सीने में क़ुतुब-शाह का किरदार भी है वज़्अ&#39;-दारी भी है इख़्लास भी है प्यार भी है उस की बाँहों में बसी भागमती की दुनिया जगमगाता है जहाँ चाँद रवा-दारी का मस्जिदें भी हैं मनादिर भी हैं गिरिजा-घर भी निकहत-ओ-नूर में डूबा हुआ हर मंज़र भी इस लिए &#39;मीर&#39; की &#39;ग़ालिब&#39; की ग़ज़ल कहते हैं शहर को आज भी सभी ताज-महल कहते हैं मशहूर शायर अमीर अहमद ख़ुसरव ने हैदराबाद को इन खूबसूरत शब्दों में परिभाषित किया है.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Modi In Kargil: &#39;अगर हमारे देश की तरफ नजर उठीं तो तीनों सेनाएं उसी भाषा में मुंहतोड़ जवाब देंगी&#39;, जानें करगिल में दिवाली मनाने पहुंचे PM मोदी ने और क्या कहा</title>
      <link>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pm-modi-in-kargil-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 06:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newsstreet.github.io/news/pm-modi-in-kargil-/</guid>
      <description>PM Modi In Kargil: &amp;lsquo;अगर हमारे देश की तरफ नजर उठीं तो तीनों सेनाएं उसी भाषा में मुंहतोड़ जवाब देंगी&amp;rsquo;, जानें करगिल में दिवाली मनाने पहुंचे PM मोदी ने और क्या कहा PM Modi In Kargil: पीएम मोदी करगिल में देश के जवानों के साथ दिवाली मना रहे हैं। इस मौके पर उन्होंने कहा कि पाकिस्तान के साथ ऐसा कोई युद्ध नहीं हुआ है, जहां करगिल ने विजय पताका नहीं फहराया है। अगर हमारे देश की तरफ नजर उठीं तो तीनों सेनाएं उसी भाषा में मुंहतोड़ जवाब देंगी।</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
